Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents G
  - Gatschet, Albert S. (Box 30)
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1907 Apr. 14
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1907 Apr. 20
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1907 May 17
    - See Le Congrés international des Americanistes, 1909 Dec.
  - Gatchet & Manning (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 6
  - Gaultier, J. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 15; 2p.
  - Gauss, Christian (Box 30)
    - From Boas
      (See Boas, F. to Carlson, A.J.)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 13; 1p.
  - Gav--, John P. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 20; 1p.
  - Gavit, J.P. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 May 15
    - From Boas, 1917 May 19
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 May 15
  - Gay, Hazel (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 30; 1p.
  - Gaynon (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
  - Geare, R.I. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1896 June 24
  - Geary, John E. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 11; 1p.
  - Gebhart, John C. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 May 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 11; 1p. + 6p. encl.
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - (enc:Memorandum on the proposed study of the relative importance of the factors of heredity and environment on the growth and development of children. Dublin, L.I. to Gebhart, J.C. Mar. 30, 1925), 1926 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 May 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 12; 1p.
    - J.C. Gebhart -- from L.I. Dublin, 1925 Mar. 30
    - (Enc. with Gebhart, J.C., Apr. 3, 1925)
  - Geddes, D.P. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1930 July 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 27; 1p.
  - Geddings, F.S. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 21
  - Geffner, Sol (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 19; 1p.
  - "Herr Geheimrath" (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1896 May 29; 3p.
  - Gehmann, R. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 11
  - Geisler, Friedrich, and Selig, Anna (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 20; 1p.
  - Gelbach, M. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 11; 4p.
  - Gelernter, Baruch (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 13; 2p.
  - Geller, Maurice (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 15; 2p.
  - Gellner-Woltmann, M. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 15; 1p.
      (Enc: Lewis, C.M. (open letter)
  - Gelpche, Marie (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1923 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 2p.
  - Genealogy (Box 30)
    - See explanatory note [re genealogy], 1935 Feb. end
  - Gennett Record Corp. (Box 30)
    - Gennett Record Corp. -- to P.E. Goddard, 1926 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Goddard, P.E., Dec. 11, 1925)
  - Genoa R. Biblioteca Universitaria (Box 30)
    - Genoa R. Biblioteca Universitaria -- to C. Gini, 1920 July 15; 1p.
  - Gentzler, W.E. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Geographical Society (Box 30)
    - Lecture, Oct. 21
  - Geographisches Gesellschaft in Hamburg President (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 28; 1p.
  - Georg, Dr. Manfred (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 10; 1p.
  - George, Rudolf (Box 30)
    - R. George -- to Ravene, 1889 Aug. 20; 3p.
  - Gerard, James W. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1911 May 26
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 17; 1p.
  - Gerberich, Albert H. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - (Enc: Garífuna language sheets.), 1938 Nov. 26; 1p.
  - Gerdau, Otto (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1904 July 7; 1p.
  - Gerdau, Mrs. Otto (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 25; 1p.
  - Gerig, J.L. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 16; 1p.
  - Gerland, George (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 12
    - To Boas, 1885 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1887 May 19
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan.; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 June 18; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1889 June 15
  - Gerlich, J.H. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 5; (telegram)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - J.H. Gerlich -- to P. Baginsky, 1933 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Baginsky, P., June 17, 1934)
  - German-American Commerce, Inc. (Box 30)
    See Harles, Heinrich
    See Shrell, C.
  - German-America emergency conference to defeat Hitler, to safeguard American democracy Program (Box 30)
    - 1942 Mar. 1, 4p.
  - German-American league for culture National executive board (Box 30)
    see also Deutschamen Kanishe Kulturverband
    - From Boas, 1940 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May; 1p.
    - (Enc: Rundschreiben Nr. 3 Oct. 1938), 1939 July 10; (telegram)
    - To Boas, 1941 July; 4p.
    - German-American league for culture. National executive committee from Bohn, Frank
    - 1940 Jan. 27
    - 1939 Dec.
  - German-American Literary Defense Com. (Box 30)
    See Weismann, Herny
  - German-American writers association (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 8; 2p.
  - German Consul General (Box 30)
    See Gneist
  - German Embassy (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 28; 1p.
  - German-Jewish Club, Inc. (Box 30)
    See Eichenberg, Alfred
  - German Liederkranz Directors (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p.
  - German professors -- (List) (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 2p.
  - German Red Cross (Box 31)
    See von Winterfeld
  - German scholars (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 18; 2p.
  - German Social Scientific Society of N.Y. (Box 31)
    See Freudenthal, Wolff
  - German Society of the City of N.Y. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 22; 1p.
  - The German Spectator (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec.; 2p.
  - Germania. President (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p.
  - Germanistic Society of America (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1904 May 7
    - From Boas, 1904 May 7
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1905-1906; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - (Att. Invitation to lecture of Prof. Fredrich Delitzsch and notice of change of hall., 1906 Jan. 15,17,19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 15,17,19
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - See Jäkel, Theo. Feb. 27, 1906, 1906 Feb. 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 20; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Jan.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan.; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan.; 8p.
    - See Heuser, F.W.J., July 2, 1931
    - See Heuser, F.W.J. to Schmidt-Ott, F., Dec. 8, 1931
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from American Relief Committee for German Children, 1920 Feb.; 2p.
      (see Hepburn, A.Burton; Metz, Herman A.; Speyer, James; and Schurz, Carl L.)
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from Wilhelm Braun, 1918 May 7; 1p.
    - Germanistic Society of -- America from Hepburn, A., 1920 Feb.; 2p.
      (Also see Metz, Herman A.; Speyer, James; Schurz, Carl L.)
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from Kraske, Ilse, 1931 June 5
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from Metz, Herman A., 1920 Feb.; 2p.
      (Also see Hepburn A. Burton; Speyer, James; Schurz, Carl L.)
    - Germanistic Society -- from Naetebus, 1920 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from Presby, Frank H., 1906 Mar. 20; 2p.
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from Schurz, Carl L., 1920 Feb.; 2p.
      (See Hepburn, Metz, Speyer,)
    - Germanistic Society -- from Simon, 1920 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 19
    - Germanistic Society of America -- from Speyer, James, 1920 Feb.; 2p.
      (See Hepburn, Metz, Schurz) *
      (Also see Butler, N.M.; Alpers, Helene; Braun, Wilhelm; Adams, Edw.D.; Buenz, Karl; Boas, Emil L.; Carpenter, W.H.; Low, Seth; Kudlich, H.C.; Tombo, Rudolf, Jr.; Weber, Leonard; White, Andrew D.)
  - Germanistic Society, Board of Directors and Officers of Germany -- To Boas, 1920 May; 1p (Box 31)
    - See Economic developments in the Third Reich, 1936 see Dec. 31
  - Germany. Ambassador. Mexico (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 12; 1p.
  - Germany, Reichs-u. Preussuschen Minister für Wissenschaft, Erziehung und Volksbildung (Box 31)
    - from Sydow, C.M. von
    - (Enclosed with Sydow, C.M., Mar. 1, 1935)
  - Germarshandson? (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 24; 1p.
  - Germenshond? (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 24; 1p.
  - Gerould, James Thayer (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - J.T. Gerould -- to Marion Leroy Burton, 1923 Jan. 29; 2p.
  - Gerrodette, F.H. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 July 5
    - To Boas, 1931 May 6; 2p.
  - Gersdorf, C.L. Baron von (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 2; 3p.
  - Geschwendt, F. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 2; 1p.
    - Gesellschaft der Wissenschaften --, Mar.5,1923; 1p
  - Gesellschaft für Erdkunde, Berlin (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 3; 1p.
  - Gesellschaft-wissenschaftlicher Verein(?) (Box 31)
    - To Boas, Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 27
  - Gessner, R. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 4; 1p
  - Gesture (Box 31)
    - See Wittenby, Gertrude. See also Symbolic Movement. Also see Kaufman, E.I., Cohen, Geo. W., 8-20 and 28, Efrong, Thone, Frank; Silverberg, M.B.;Environmental Influences... Nationality Difference...,Postural Difference...,Motor Habits, DeOnes, Fedenis, 8-7-36; 9-14-36; 8-28-36; 10-23-36; 3-6-35; 3-7-35; 3-8-35; 3-8-35; 6-30-36.
  - Gesture and Posture, 1935 Mar. 6; 2p (Box 31)
  - Gettell, R.G. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 16; 1p.
  - Gettemy, C.F. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 10
  - Getty, Lillian B. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p.
  - Geyer, Robert (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 2; 1p.
  - Ghent. Staatsuniversiteit te Gent. (Box 31)
    - See Bessemans, A, 1934 Nov. 7
  - Ghose, S.N. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 11; 1p.
  - Gibbons, James (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p.
  - Gibbs, D.S. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 11; 1p.
  - Gibson, J. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 22
  - Giddings, F.H. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 28
  - Gideonse, Harry D. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - H.D. Gideonse -- to Amer, Comm. for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1941 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Gideonse, H.D. Copy Gideonse, H.D. to Shapley, H. Copy Letter (photostat) by...Faculty of Brooklyn College), Oct. 22, 1941. Oct. 22, 1941.
    - H.D. Gideonse -- to Brooklyn College.Faculty, 1941 Nov. 25; 5p.
    - H.D. Gideonse -- from A.J. Carlson, 1941 Oct. 11
    - H.D. Gideonse -- from Clyde R. Miller, 1941 Oct. 15
    - H.D. Gideonse -- to H. Shapley, 1941 Oct. 22; 2p.
  - Gidley, J.W. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 27; 1p.
  - Gies, William J. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - W.J. Gies -- from M. Dewey, 1918 Mar. 23
    - W.J. Gies -- from L.M. Waugh, 1918 Mar. 17
    - W.J. Gies -- from J. Lowe Young, 1918 Apr. 4
  - Giesbrecht, W. (Box 31)
    - W. Giesbrecht -- to Toni Boas, 1883 June 16
  - Giese, P. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 8; 1p.
      (Enc: Giese, P. to Anon)
    - P. Giese -- to Anon (Cabanellas?)
    - (Enc. with Giese, P., July 8, 1931)
  - Gieseler, W. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 13; 2p.
  - University Library of Giessen (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p.
  - Gifford, E.W. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - (Attached: budget for 1928), 1929 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - (Attached: Sapir, E. to Gifford, E.W., Dec. 2, 1930)
    - E.W. Gifford -- from Jeannette C. Robbins, 1927 July 19; 1p.
    - E.W. Gifford -- from Jeannette C. Robbins, 1927 July 24; 1p.
    - E.W. Gifford -- from E.Sapir, 1930 Dec. 2
    - (Attached to Gifford, E.W., Dec. 26, 1930)
  - Gifford, James P. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas
    - (See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, Feb. 11, 1937)
  - Gilbert, Walter M. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1905 June 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 June 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 May 27
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - (Enc:Gilbert, W.M. to Jochelson, W. Mar. 15, 1934), 1934 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - W.M. Gilbert -- to W. Jochelson, 1934 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Gilbert, W.M., Mar. 15, 1934)
  - Gilbert, William H. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 13; 1p.
  - Gilder, Richard Watson (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1906 Sept. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept.7
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 May 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 May 22
  - Gildersleeve, V.C. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 June 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 May 21
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 21; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 May 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 June 23
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - (Enc: Budget and covering letter), 1919 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Columbia Univ. Multigraph Dept. bill Nov. 22, 1919), 1920 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - (Enc: Budget sheet), 1933 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 28; 1p.
  - GilFillan, J.A. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 16; 3p.
  - GilFillan, S.C. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 1p.
  - Gill, DeLancey (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 19
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1917 May 26
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 29
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 May 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec.; 1p.
    - D. Gill -- from J.W. Fewkes, 1917 Dec.
    - D. Gill -- from J.W. Fewkes, 1917 Dec.
    - D. Gill -- to J.W. Fewkes, 1923 June 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Fewkes, J.W., June 28, 1923)
    - D. Gill -- to S. Searles, 1927 June 16; 2p.
    - (Enc. originally with Searles, S., June 24, 1927)
  - Gill, Laura (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 27
    - (Enc: Boas, F. to Butler, N.M., Sept. 27, 1905)
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 1
  - Gill, R. C. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 5; 1p.
  - Gillett, Charles R. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1906 May 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 25; 1p.
  - Gillett, E.C. (Mrs. S.W.) (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1931 June 17; 1p.
  - Gillett, F.H. (Box 31)
    - F.H. Gillett -- to E.C. Parsons, 1929 June 14; 1p.
    - F.H. Gillett -- to E.C. Parsons, 1929 June 21; 1p.
  - Gillette, H.M. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 31; 1p.
  - Gillin, J.L. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 14; 1p.
  - Gillis, Adolph (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 19; 1p.
  - Gillis, J.M. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 10; 1p.
  - Gilman, Daniel C. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1902 Oct. 28; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 10
  - Gilson, E. (Box 31)
    - See Bouglé, C., Mar. 15, 1931
  - Gilson, Mary B. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 17; 1p.
  - Mrs. Gimbel, Louis S., Jr. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Gimpera, P.B. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 20; 1p.
  - Gini, Corrado (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept.6; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 29; 1p.
    - (Enc: List No. 1 - American Social Progress Series - 5p. List No. 2 - Gabinetto di Statistica), 1920 Aug. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 25; (postcard)
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar.; 2p.
    - (Attached: Paper on demography.), 1931 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: International congress for studies regarding population 1931), 1937 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - C. Gini -- from Bresciano, G., 1920 June 30
    - C. Gini -- from J. Carta, 1920 July 6
    - To Boas, 1920 July 12
    - C. Gini -- from Genoa. R. Biblioteca Univ., 1920 July 15
    - C. Gini -- from G. Oliva, 1920 July 7
  - Ginn & Company (Box 31)
    - Ginn & Company -- to Julius Bien & Co., 1889 Feb. 5
  - Ginzberg, Louis (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 1; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Giodíry (?) (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 14
  - Girard, Rafael (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 10; 2p.
  - Girneff, N. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 12; 2p.
  - Girty, G.H. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 15; 1p.
  - Gissler (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 6; 2p.
  - Givens, W.E. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 27; 1p.
  - Gladys (Box 31)
    See Reichard, Gladys A.
  - Glasmeier, H. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1926 June 7; 2p.
  - Glassman, L.M. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 23; 1p.
  - Glauerman, I. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p.
  - Glauning, O. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 27; 1p.
  - Glenn, J.M. (Box 31)
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
  - Glogau, Otto (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 7; 2p.
  - Glück, H. (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1924 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 30; 1p.
  - Glueck, Sheldon (Box 31)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 16; 1p.